A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - Societies, Institutions, Associations, 1946-1948
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - American Neurological Association, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - American Philosophical Society (APS), 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - APS, Committee on Research, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - American Philosophical Society (APS), Sigma Xi Committee on Grants-in-Aid, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - APS, Sigma Xi Investigation of Research, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - APS, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Electroencephalography, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Association of American Physicians, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Applicants, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Applicants - Graduate School, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Applicant - Adler, John C., 1948 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), Advisory Committee for Biology and Medicine, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - AEC, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - AEC, Universities, 1948-1948 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Bibliography, Bronk, D.W., 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Bishop, David W., 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Condon, E.U., 1948 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Air Safety Research, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Draft, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Foundations Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Harvey, E. Newton, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Hecht, Selig, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Institute for Cancer Research, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Jacobson, W., 1948 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Jasper, Herbert, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - John Morgan Society, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Journal of Neurological Sciences, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Kuffler, Stephen W., 1948 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - M.I.T. Visiting Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - National Heart Bill, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - National Academy of Science, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - NAS, Membership, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - NAS, Mission for the Exchange of Industrial Technology, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - National Research Council, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - NRC, Academy-Research Council Expansion, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - NRC, Biological Institute, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - NRC, Science Abroad, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - NRC, Symposium, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Naval Research Advisory Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - National Science Foundation, 1946-1947 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - NSF Legislation, Panel, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - National Science Fund, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Pennsylvania Institute of Neurology, Objectives and Organization, undated (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Prosthetic Devices, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Prostigmine Conference, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Psychophysiological Laboratory, Institute for Juvenile Research, undated (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - The Review of Scientific Instruments, 1946-1948 (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Richards, A. Newton, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 58)
    - Scientific American, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 59)
    - Sigma Xi, 1945-1948 (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, Proceedings, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Sydenham Medical Coterie, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - University of PA, Medical Board of Hospital, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - University of PA, Medical School, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - University of PA, Physics Department, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 65)
    - University of PA, Committee on Radioactive Isotopes, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 66)
  - CAM, Senate Hearing, Russian-Egyptian Trip - 1945, The Royal Society Tercentenary - 1960
    - Chambers, Leslie, Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Rawson, A.J., Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Bronk Miscellaneous, Reports, Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Bronk Miscellaneous, Army-Navy, 1943-1944 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Headquarters of Armed Forces, 1943-1944 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Hearings Before the Select Committee on Post-War Military Policy, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Headquarters Eighth Air Force, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Air Forces in Europe (Germany), 1945 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Demobilization, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, June 1945, American Philosophical Society, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Russian-Egyptian Trip, 1945 June (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - British Association, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Bronk Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - The Royal Society, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - The Royal Society, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Miscellaneous, 1921-1960 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - University of Hawaii, Hawaii Institute of Geophysics, Sep 1, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - "Idea That Science Can Solve Everything Is a False One", 1960 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Bronk Miscellaneous - Graduate Programs, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Clippings (photocopies), 1926-1971
    - University of Pennsylvania, Medical Department, 1877-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1931-1937 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Bronk Clippings, Articles, 1941-1947 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1926-1947 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1958-1963 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Bronk Clippings, Scrapbook, 1945-1949 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Bronk Clippings, Atoms for Peace, 1958-1966 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Bronk Clippings, Rockefeller University, 1958-1965 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Bronk Clippings, Space Science Board, 1957-1958 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1950-1963 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified Bronk Clippings, undated (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Clippings (photocopies), 1955-1963
    - International Conference on the Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - International Conference on the Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Bronk Clippings, U.S. Satellites, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1956 January-June (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1956 July-December (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1957 January-July (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1957 July-December (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Bronk Clippings, Housing, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Bronk Clippings, Russian Satellite, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Bronk Clippings, Satellite "Explorer", 1958 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Bronk Clippings, Fallout and Radiation, 1956-1958 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Clippings, Rockefeller Institute Diet, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Bronk Clippings, Artificial Internal Organs, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1958 January-April (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1958 May-June (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1958 July-September (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1958 October-December (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1959 January-April (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1959 May-June (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1959 July-December (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1960 January-May (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1960 June-October (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1960 November-December (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1962 January-May (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1962 June-December (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1963 January-May (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1963 June-December (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Honorary Memberships, 1952-1975
    - International Benjamin Franklin Society, Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Lafayette and Lake Forest, 1956-1960 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - University of London, 1960-1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Louvaine University, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - University of Maryland, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Miami University, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Mills College, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - New School for Social Research, 1958-1960 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - University of the State of New York, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Northwestern University; Notre Dame; The University of PA, 1948-1953 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Oberlin College, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1974-1974 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Princeton University, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - The Queen's University, Belfast, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Reed College, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller University, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Toledo University, Science Bldg, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Ursinus College, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Widener College (formerly PA Military College), 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Yale University, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Yeshiva University, 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Membership Cards, 1960s-1970s (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - New York State Public Health Council, 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - New York State Public Health Council, 1970-1973 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - New York State Public Health Council, 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - New York State Public Health Council, Health, Manpower and Interprofessional Relations Committee, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Notes for Speeches, undated (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Office of University Relations, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Office of University Relations, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Office of University Relations, 1970-1972 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Office of University Relations, Urban Research Inventory, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Sherman Fairchild Distinguished Scholar Appointment, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Universities and Secondary Schools, 1954-1975
    - University Research Association, Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - University Research Association, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Adelphi University, 1958-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Australian Universities, Bronx High School of Science, Katherine Branson School, 1958-1966 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of California, California Institute of Technology, 1966-1972 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Case Institute, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Claremont College, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, College of the Atlantic, University of Connecticut, 1971-1975 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Cornell Centennial, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Dartmouth College, 1961-1965 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Dickinson College, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, The Dropsie College, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Eisenhower College, 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Fordham University, Hamilton College, 1961-1970 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Long Island University, Mackinac College, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Manhattan Community College, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1956-1971 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of Michigan, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Mills College, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of Missouri, National University, City University of New York, 1958-1966 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, The University of the State of New York, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, State University of New York, 1958-1967 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, New York University, 1951-1967 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Notre Dame, Penn State University, PA Military Colleges, Woman's Medical College of PA, 1965-1967 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of Pittsburgh, 1956-1958 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1959-1973 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Pomona College, 1961-1967 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Princeton University, 1951-1967 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Purdue University, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Reed College, 1957-1958 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Rutgers University, St. Bonaventure University, 1958-1966 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Sarah Lawrence College, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Smith College, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of South Carolina, Stevens Institute of Technology, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Swarthmore College, 1954-1975 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Syracuse University, 1969-1975 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, University of Texas, Ursinus College, Vanderbilt University, University of Vermont, Wake Forest College, University of Washington, 1959-1968 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Western Reserve University, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Williams College, 1968-1972 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Universities & Secondary Schools, Yale University, 1955-1968 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - National Academy of Science, Presidential Activities, 1954-1975
    - National Academy of Science (NAS), Barnard Medal Committee, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - NAS, Board of Medicine Study, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - NAS, Buildings, 1961-1966 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - NAS, Buildings, 1961-1966 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - NAS, Centennial Speeches, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - NAS, Committee to Examine Sectional Structure of Class II, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - NAS, Consortium for Receiving Lunar Samples, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1950-1962 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - NAS, Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - NAS, Council for the Advancement of Scientific Writing, 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - NAS, Home Secretary, Bronk Portrait, 1963-1966 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - NAS, Home Secretary, Jewett Portrait, 1956-1959 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - NAS, Hugh Dryden Fund Committee, 1965-1971 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - NAS, Luncheon for Romanian Scientists, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - NAS, Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - NAS, Meeting, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - NAS, Membership Analysis, 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - NAS, NAS-Bulgarian Academy of Sciences Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - NAS, NAS, NAS-Royal Society Discussions, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - NAS, NAS-Sloan Basic Research Symposium, 1958-1959 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - NAS, New Building Prospects, 1959-1968 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - NAS, Newton Richards Fund, 1967-1972 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - NAS, Personal File, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - NAS, Personnel, 1959-1967 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - NAS, Portraits - Lillie, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - NAS, Proposed Program in International Relations, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - NAS, Retirement Letters, Meid & Trytten, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - NAS, Romania & Bulgaria Trip, 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - NAS, Scientific Advisory Board, USAF, 1954-1957 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - NAS, William Shockley, 1966-1969 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology re Manuscripts, 1949-1955
    - Manuscripts for Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology (JCCP) -L, 1950-1952 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Ms: Ladd, Michael; Raisz, Lawrence G.; Crowder, Charles H.; Page, Lot B., circa 1952 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Ms: Leonard, W.R., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Ms: Ling, Gilbert & Gerard, R.W., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Mss: Lorente de No, Rafael, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Ms: Manery, J.F., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ms: Marmont, George, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Mss: Marshak, Alfred, 1948-1950 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Ms: Nastuk, William L., 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Mss: Newcomer, W.S.; Norman, Amos; Nowinski, Wibtor; Noell, Werner; Nevenberger, John; Nardone, Roland M.; Nachmansohn, David, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Ms: Poe, Charles F., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Mss: Praglin, Julius; Patt, Harvey M.; Paigen, Kenneth; Parpart, Arthur K.; Porter, John W.; Pearson, William N.; Puck, Theodore T.; Parrack, Horace O.; Parker, Raymond C; Pletsch, Don, 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Postage for Manuscripts, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Mss: Quastler, Henry, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Mss: Rossi, Harald; Rugh, Roberts; Rosenblith, Walter A., 1951-1952 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Mss: Ream, James S., 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Ms: Richards, Glenn A., 1949-1952 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Ms: Rockstein, Morris, 1949-1951 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Ms: Ronkin, R.R., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Ms: Rosenblueth, Arturo, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Ms: Ross, Morris H., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Ms: Schmidt-Neilsen, Knut, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Ms: Schrank, A.R., 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Ms: Scheer, Bradley T., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Ms: Seaman, Gerald R., 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Ms: Sherman, Frederick G., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Ms: Sjostrand, Fritiof S., 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Ms: Smith, Arthur H., 1949-1951 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Ms: Swank, Roy L, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Mss: Supplements, 1948-1953 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-S, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-T, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Mss: Tobias, Julian M., 1949-1952 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Ms: Lasaki, Ichiji, 1949-1951 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Ms: Villee, Charles A., 1949-1952 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Ms: Von Brand, Theodor, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Ms: von Dach, Herman, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Ms: van Weel, P.B.; Vernberg, John F.; von Euler, Curt; van Harreveld, A.; van Alphen, G.W.H.M., 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Ms: Wright, Ernest B., 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Ms: Miscellaneous-W, 1949-1952 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Mss: Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Mss: Zirkle, Raymond E.; Zeuthen, Erik, 1951-1953 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-B, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-C, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-D, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-E, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-F, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-H, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Ms: Ichioka, Masamichi, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-K, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-L, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-M, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Mss: Peskin, James C., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Mss: Ream, James S., 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 54)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-R, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-S, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 56)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-T, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 57)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-V, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 58)
    - Mss: Miscellaneous-W, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 59)
    - Mss: Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology (JCCP), 1953-1955 (Box 67, Folder 60)
    - Mss Published in June 1954 JCCP, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 61)
    - Mss Accepted and Published in August 1954 JCCP, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 62)
    - Mss Accepted and Published in October 1954 JCCP (Box 67, Folder 63)
    - Mss for Publication in JCCP, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 64)
    - Mss for Publication in JCCP, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 65)
    - Mss: Review Editors JCCP, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 66)
    - Mss Returned to Authors for Revision, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 67)
    - Mss: The Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 68)
    - Managing Editor (Bronk's Successor) of JCCP, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 69)
    - JCCP, 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 70)
  - Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology re Manuscripts, 1933-1953
    - JCCP, 1933-1935 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - JCCP - Rejected Manuscripts, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - JCCP - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - JCCP - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - JCCP - Manuscripts Sent to Referees for Correction, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - JCCP - Mss, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - JCCP - Mss, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - JCCP - Published Mss (Listed), 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, A-B, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, C-D, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, E, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, F, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, G, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, H-I, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, J, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, K, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, L, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, M, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, N-O-P, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - JCCP - Correspondence re Mss, R, 1944-1945 (Box 68, Folder 20)